Catepec de Morelos, State of México, 55520, México

\$5572742865

Profile

Software developer with two years of experience looking for growth in a personal and professional way as a full stack developer, I have developed desktop applications although I also have knowledge about web development, using JavaScript and React as front-end, for back-end C# and Java and for databases MySQL, SQLite, SQL Server and JSON for cloud technologies,I have international certification in Azure fundamentals.

Employment History

.Net Developer, Developware, Mexico City

May 2022 — Present

Valuita, Remote

November 2020 — January 2022

Payment Systems Analyst, Bank of Mexico, Mexico

August 2020 — May 2022

Design and implementation of software tools for processes that are already established in the area, Monitoring and Operation of payment systems, Validate the new versions of payment systems, attend business continuity tests; React quickly and efficiently to incidents within the area.

Informatic Technician, QPlus, Mexico City

June 2015 — August 2018

Generated data backup for computers, uninstalled and installed computer equipment, installed software on computer equipment; I led and trained the installation of the programs that caused the most problems, which helped customers to be satisfied with their equipment and solving problems that they had with the computers already installed.

Education

Bachelor's Degree, National Taiwan University of Science and Technology, Taipei

August 2018 — January 2019

I participated in international internship: I studied six months in Taiwan getting to know the culture and practicing English

Computer Systems Engineering, Superior School of Computing, IPN, Mexico August 2015 — December 2019

Completed studies.

Computer Technician, Vocacional 3, State of Mexico

August 2022 — May 2015

Completed studies.



Hobbies

English

I like to continue training myself by taking courses to learn new ways to do my activities, also I enjoy keeping myself updated with the tools that are new about programming.

Certifications

AZ-900: Microsoft Azure Fundamentals, Innovaccion, Microsoft.

May 2021 — June 2021

Courses

 $\label{eq:total-total-total-total} \textbf{ITAM, Web, CDMX: Process analysis and improvement, Mexico City}$

November 2021

Microsoft Certificate of Achievement: Web : Az - 303: Microsoft Azure Architect Technologies, Mexico City

September 2021

Microsoft Certificate of Achievement: Web : Az - 304: Microsoft Azure Architect Design

September 2021

References

Diego Barbosa from CitiBanamex diego.marvin@gmail.com | 5540067867

Jose Reyes from Banco de México 5583682795

Luis Rodrigo Salazar from Nuxiba rod.salazar.vazquez@gmail.com | 5539337594